solve_two_pow_8:
  question: "2‚Å∏"
  answer: '256'
  reward: 'random'
threefourfivesix:
  question: "34+56"
  answer: '90'
  reward: 'random'
seventwoeightnine:
  question: "72+89"
  answer: '161'
  reward: 'random'
fourfiveseveneight:
  question: "45+78"
  answer: '123'
  reward: 'random'
sixsixeightseven:
  question: "66+87"
  answer: '153'
  reward: 'random'
nineonefiveeight:
  question: "91+58"
  answer: '149'
  reward: 'random'
fivetimestwenty:
  question: "5*21"
  answer: '105'
  reward: 'random'
ninetimesnine:
  question: "9*9"
  answer: '81'
  reward: 'random'
sixtysix_times_eleven:
  question: "66*11"
  answer: '726'
  reward: 'random'
ninetyoneminustwenty:
  question: "91-20"
  answer: '71'
  reward: 'random'
seventyminusninetyeight:
  question: "70-98"
  answer: '-28'
  reward: 'random'
onehundredandtwentythree_minus_seventyeight:
  question: "123-78"
  answer: '45'
  reward: 'random'
58_plus_342:
  question: "58+342"
  answer: '400'
  reward: 'random'
76_plus_129:
  question: "76+129"
  answer: '205'
  reward: 'random'
91_plus_507:
  question: "91+507"
  answer: '598'
  reward: 'random'